{
  "Entities": [
    {
      "Reason": "the text mentioned 'St. John the Baptist'",
      "Type": "PERSON",
      "Name": "St John the Baptist"
    },
    {
      "Reason": "the text mentioned 'Leonardo painted his... 'Last Supper''",
      "Type": "ARTWORK",
      "Name": "Last Supper"
    },
    {
      "Reason": "the text mentioned 'magnificently painted, and by Leonardo'",
      "Type": "PERSON",
      "Name": "Leonardo"
    },
    {
      "Reason": "the text mentioned 'In the National Gallery version'",
      "Type": "LOCATION",
      "Name": "the National Gallery"
    },
    {
      "Reason": "the text mentioned 'chef d'oeuvre'",
      "Type": "ARTWORK",
      "Name": "chef d'oeuvre"
    },
    {
      "Reason": "the text mentioned 'for the end wall of the Refectory of the Dominican Convent of S. Maria delle Grazie at Milan'",
      "Type": "LOCATION",
      "Name": "Refectory of the Dominican Convent of S. Maria delle Grazie at Milan"
    },
    {
      "Reason": "the text mentioned 'the feet of the Christ'",
      "Type": "PERSON",
      "Name": "Christ"
    },
    {
      "Reason": "the text mentioned 'one Michelangelo Belotti'",
      "Type": "PERSON",
      "Name": "Michelangelo Belotti"
    },
    {
      "Reason": "the text mentioned 'at Milan'",
      "Type": "LOCATION",
      "Name": "Milan"
    },
    {
      "Reason": "the text mentioned 'Professor Cavenaghi'",
      "Type": "PERSON",
      "Name": "Professor Cavenaghi"
    },
    {
      "Reason": "the text mentioned 'the fresco was again restored by Mazza'",
      "Type": "PERSON",
      "Name": "Mazza"
    },
    {
      "Reason": "the text mentioned 'Napoleon's cavalry'",
      "Type": "PERSON",
      "Name": "Napoleon"
    }
  ],
  "Relationships": [
    {
      "From": {
        "Reason": null,
        "Type": "PERSON",
        "Name": "Leonardo"
      },
      "To": {
        "Reason": null,
        "Type": "ARTWORK",
        "Name": "Last Supper"
      },
      "Relationship": "PAINTED",
      "Reason": "the text mentioned 'Between 1496 and 1498 Leonardo painted his... 'Last Supper''"
    },
    {
      "From": {
        "Reason": null,
        "Type": "ARTWORK",
        "Name": "Last Supper"
      },
      "To": {
        "Reason": null,
        "Type": "LOCATION",
        "Name": "Refectory of the Dominican Convent of S. Maria delle Grazie at Milan"
      },
      "Relationship": "LIVED_IN",
      "Reason": "the text mentioned 'for the end wall of the Refectory of the Dominican Convent of S. Maria delle Grazie at Milan'"
    },
    {
      "From": {
        "Reason": null,
        "Type": "PERSON",
        "Name": "Leonardo"
      },
      "To": {
        "Reason": null,
        "Type": "ARTWORK",
        "Name": "Last Supper"
      },
      "Relationship": "PAINTED",
      "Reason": "Leonardo painted his chef d'oeuvre, the 'Last Supper'"
    },
    {
      "From": {
        "Reason": null,
        "Type": "ARTWORK",
        "Name": "Last Supper"
      },
      "To": {
        "Reason": null,
        "Type": "LOCATION",
        "Name": "Refectory of the Dominican Convent of S. Maria delle Grazie at Milan"
      },
      "Relationship": "LIVED_IN",
      "Reason": "for the end wall of the Refectory of the Dominican Convent of S. Maria delle Grazie at Milan"
    },
    {
      "From": {
        "Reason": null,
        "Type": "PERSON",
        "Name": "Michelangelo Belotti"
      },
      "To": {
        "Reason": null,
        "Type": "ARTWORK",
        "Name": "Last Supper"
      },
      "Relationship": "RESTORED",
      "Reason": "In 1726 one Michelangelo Belotti, an obscure Milanese painter, received £300 for the worthless labour he bestowed on restoring it"
    },
    {
      "From": {
        "Reason": null,
        "Type": "PERSON",
        "Name": "Mazza"
      },
      "To": {
        "Reason": null,
        "Type": "ARTWORK",
        "Name": "Last Supper"
      },
      "Relationship": "RESTORED",
      "Reason": "In 1770 the fresco was again restored by Mazza"
    },
    {
      "From": {
        "Reason": null,
        "Type": "PERSON",
        "Name": "Professor Cavenaghi"
      },
      "To": {
        "Reason": null,
        "Type": "ARTWORK",
        "Name": "Last Supper"
      },
      "Relationship": "RESTORED",
      "Reason": "In October 1908 Professor Cavenaghi completed"
    }
  ]
}